I'm Kent Bull and my session was KERIA
tutorial talking about how to set up a
KERIA server, what a Signify client is,
and how to make a basic lightweight wallet
with Signify and KERIA. What I do
differently now as a consequence of being
in the KERIA space is I aggressively adopt
zero passwords, no shared secrets. And I
challenge myself to say, when I think I
need a password, how can I replace that
with the signature? If Signify TS and
KERIA disappeared, what the self-sovereign
identity community would lose would be a
lightweight wallet implementation that
makes it easy for a low barrier of entry
and people to adopt this sort of
architecture. And so we'd have to re
-engineer a server architecture with an
agent and a lightweight wallet
implementation. It's very useful for
certain, I would say constrained contexts
useful technology, we'd have to re
-engineer it, but that's what we'd lose if
Signify and KERIA were to go away today.
Thank you.